escapade.co.uk 2018-01-31

# Privacy Policy - Escapade | Escapade® UK

(Your statutory customer rights are not affected.)

At Escapade we are committed to protecting your privacy and we comply with the data protection laws applicable to the UK. This Privacy Policy outlines how your personal information is treated and forms part of our Terms and Conditions. (We may occasionally modify our Privacy Policy; when this happens we will notify you via our terms and conditions page).

## What information do we collect?

When you order we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery/billing address. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and notify you of the order status. We also ask you for your telephone number(s) so that we can contact you easily if required. As an extra measure of security we do not collect/store any credit card information. If you are concerned about your data, you have the right subject to the payment of a small fee (currently £10) to request access to the personal data which we ma hold or process about you. You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data, block or delete your data free of charge.

## How do we use your information?

Any personal data relating to you will be used and recorded by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this Privacy Policy. We use the information collected from you to process orders and to provide a more personalised shopping experience. We may use your personal information to communicate with you, for record keeping purposes, and in aggregate (and therefore anonymously) for market research purposes, to track activity on our site, to publish trends and/or to improve usefulness and content.

We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others unless you have consented to us making your name and address available to carefully vetted companies.

## In Addition

We would also like to send you offers for goods or services from Escapade or others from time to time which we think you may find of interest. If you do not wish to receive this information, do not tick the opt-in box on our checkout page before submitting your order.

## Accessing your order information

After making a purchase from Escapade we store the contract of your purchase and will send you the details of your order as well as our general terms via e-mail. You can find the terms on our website at all times. You can also easily access the details of your recent orders in your Escapade customer account.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files that a web site transfers to a site visitor’s hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking web site usage. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person’s name or e-mail address. In order to measure the effectiveness of our on-line presence, Escapade may use cookies to identify repeat visitors to our site and to determine the path visitors take on our site. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. We use the Google Analytics web tool which is capable of creating pseudonyms for user profiles.

Use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you can set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.
